Goodspeed Musicals Scherer Library of Musical Theatre Priority Archive
Goodspeed Musicals
- Inventory
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fifteen, Number Four (Winter 1999/2000); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 88; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006894 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Sixteen, Number Three (Fall 2000); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 84; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006910 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Thirteen, Number Three (Fall 1997); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006977 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Sixteen, Number Two (Summer 2000); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 92; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007033 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Sixteen, Number One (Spring 2000); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007108 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Sixteen, Number Four (Winter 2000-01); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007207 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Six, Number Two (Summer 1988); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 68; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006407 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eight, Number One (Spring 1992); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006423 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Nine, Number Three (Fall 1993); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006449 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fifteen, Number Two (Summer 1999); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006480 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume 10, Number One (Spring 1994); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 68; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006498 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eight, Number Three (Fall 1992); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006514 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume 10, Number Four (Winter 1994/95); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006555 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume 10, Number Two (Summer 1994); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006571 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume 10, Number Three (Fall 1994); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006589 (Box 10*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Twelve, Number Three (Fall 1996); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006969 (Box 10*)
  - Along Broadway, undated; The Edison Musical Magazine April 1921; Items: 1; Format: Magazine; Page count: 12; Dimensions: 6 x 9; Barcode: 35111000000996 (Box 11*)
  - Stage Favorites Part 1, undated; 1894 Collection of articles and portraits of artists from 1890-1900; Items: 1; Format: Magazine; Page count: 19; Dimensions: 9.25 x 12.5; Barcode: 35111000001044 (Box 11*)
  - Stage Favorites Part II, undated; 1894 Collection of articles and portraits of artists from 1890-1900; Items: 1; Format: Magazine; Page count: 19; Dimensions: 9.25 x 12.5; Barcode: 35111000001051 (Box 11*)
  - Stage Favorites Part III, undated; 1894 Collection of articles and portraits of artists from 1890-1900; Items: 1; Format: Magazine; Page count: 20; Dimensions: 9.25 x 12.5; Barcode: 35111000001069 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Two, Number Two (December 1982); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 12; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006290 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Two, Number Three (March 1983); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006308 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Two, Number Four (June 1983); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 14; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006316 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eight, Number Four (Winter 1992/93); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006464 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fifteen, Number Three (Fall 1999); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 78; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006472 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Nine, Number One (Spring 1993); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 68; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006506 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Nine, Number Four (Winter 1993/94); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006522 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eight, Number Two (Summer 1992); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006548 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Twelve, Number One (Spring 1996); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 75; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006803 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eleven, Number Three (Fall 1995); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006829 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eleven, Number One (Spring 1995); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006845 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Twelve, Number Two (Summer 1996); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006928 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eighteen, Number Three (Fall 2002); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006951 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eighteen, Number One (Spring 2002); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007025 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eighteen, Number Two (Summer 2002); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 92; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007041 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eleven, Number Four (Winter 1995/96); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007074 (Box 11*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Eleven, Number Two (Summer 1995); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007082 (Box 11*)
  - West Side Story, undated; Original Partiture and New Balcony Scene Music; Items: 1; Format: Partiture; Page count: 1 & 24 & 690; Dimensions: 8.75X11 & 11X14 & 17X11; Barcode: 35111000004741 (Box 12*)
  - Annie (1976), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording. 2 CDs--Act 1 (13 tracks) and Act 2 (12 tracks); Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions:; Barcode: 35111000006696 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Max Showalter Small Journal, undated; Scan journals and use OCR to put into Word document (if possible).Four bound journals in hologram.; Items: 1; Format: Journals of This Is the Army Journals of This Is the Army Journals of This Is the Army Journals of This Is the Army Journals of This Is the Army; Page count: 160; Dimensions: 3.5 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003883 (Box 13*)
  - Max Showalter oversized pages, undated; Scan journals and use OCR to put into Word document (if possible).Four bound journals in hologram.; Items: 1; Format: Scrapbook; Page count: 5; Dimensions: 6x8; Barcode: 35111000004477 (Box 13*)
  - Max Showalter Additional pages, undated; Scan journals and use OCR to put into Word document (if possible).Four bound journals in hologram.; Items: 1; Format: Scrapbook; Page count: 5; Dimensions: 6x8; Barcode: 35111000004568 (Box 13*)
  - Max Showalter Journal #1, undated; Scan journals and use OCR to put into Word document (if possible).Four bound journals in hologram.; Items: 1; Format: Journals of This Is the Army; Page count: 282; Dimensions: 6x8; Barcode: 35111000004691 (Box 13*)
  - Max Showalter Journal #2, undated; Scan journals and use OCR to put into Word document (if possible).Four bound journals in hologram.; Items: 1; Format: Journals of This Is the Army; Page count: 300; Dimensions: 6x8; Barcode: 35111000004709 (Box 13*)
  - Max Showalter Journal #3, undated; Scan journals and use OCR to put into Word document (if possible).Four bound journals in hologram.; Items: 1; Format: Journals of This Is the Army; Page count: 153; Dimensions: 6x8; Barcode: 35111000004717 (Box 13*)
  - Max Showalter Scrapbook, undated; Photos scanned in hi res and captioned accordingly; Items: 1; Format: Scrapbook of This Is the Army; Page count: 115; Dimensions: 11x14; Barcode: 35111000004758 (Box 14*)
  - GOH Archival Script "Very Good Eddie", undated; Marked by Jess Gregg & Bill Gile; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 91; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000657 (Box 15*)
  - GOH Archival Script "Oh, Kay!", undated; Archival script of 1989 Goodspeed production of Oh, Kay!; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 88; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000665 (Box 15*)
  - GOH Archival Script "Going Up", undated; Archival script of the 1976 Goodspeed production of Going Up; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 93; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000673 (Box 15*)
  - GOG Archival Script "Whoopee", undated; Archival script of the 1978 Goodspeed production of Whoopee!; Items: 1; Format: Calling Script; Page count: 130; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000681 (Box 15*)
  - GOH Archival Script "DuBerry Was A Lady", undated; Archival script of the 1974 Goodspeed production of Dubarry Was a Lady; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 104; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000699 (Box 15*)
  - GOH Archival Script "Annie", undated; Goodspeed's original first draft 3/23/1973 (Charles Strousse copy); Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 124; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000001028 (Box 15*)
  - GOH Archival Script "Hubba Hubba", undated; Archival Goodspeed script of their 1971 production of Hubba Hubba; Items: 1; Format: Calling Script; Page count: 83; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000707 (Box 16*)
  - GOH Archival Script "Lady, Be Good (1987), undated; Goodspeed's archival copy of Lady, Be Good!; Items: 1; Format: Calling Script; Page count: 109; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000715 (Box 16*)
  - GOH Archival Script "Tip Toes", undated; Goodspeed archival script from their 1978 production of Tip Toes; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 93; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000723 (Box 16*)
  - GOH Archival Script " The Five O'clock Girl", undated; Goodspeed archival script for their 1979 production of The Five O'Clock Girl; Items: 1; Format: Calling Script; Page count: 125; Dimensions: 11X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000731 (Box 16*)
  - Oklahoma!, undated; Screen Play adapted by Sonya Levien & Willian Ludwig; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 135; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000000855 (Box 16*)
  - How To Succeed In Business, undated; Max Showalter V.T.R. Script Mar 15, 1975; Items: 1; Format: V.T.R. Script; Page count: 64; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000000863 (Box 16*)
  - I've Never Been So Happy (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration(Cut at GOH); Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 14; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001762 (Box 17*)
  - That's The Way It Goes (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration (Cut at GOH); Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 17; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001770 (Box 17*)
  - Maybe (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 13; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001788 (Box 17*)
  - I Know I'm Gonna Like It Here (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 23; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001796 (Box 17*)
  - Just Wait (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration(Modified to Little Girls on Broadway); Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 11; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001804 (Box 17*)
  - Apples, Apples (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration (cut at GOH); Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 15; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001812 (Box 17*)
  - False Parents Reprise (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration (cut at GOH); Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 25; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001820 (Box 17*)
  - He Doesn't Know (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration (cut at GOH); Items: 1; Format: Music manuscript; Page count: 14; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000001838 (Box 17*)
  - Dance Sections from AnnieDance Sections from Annie, undated; Dance sections, Russell Warner's original orchestrations for GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopyDance sections, Russell Warner's original orchestrations for GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 17; Dimensions: 9 x 12; Barcode: 35111000006704 (Box 17*)
  - Hard Knock Life Vocal Selection & Dance, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Music manuscript; Page count: 20; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006720 (Box 17*)
  - We Got Annie Vocal Selection, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006746 (Box 17*)
  - Just Wait! Vocal Selection, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006753 (Box 17*)
  - Something Was Missing (Vocal Selections), undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 9; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006837 (Box 17*)
  - NYC (Vocal Selection), undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11 & 8.5 x 14; Barcode: 35111000006902 (Box 17*)
  - NYC, undated; From GOH's original production of Annie; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 40; Dimensions: 8.5 x 8.75 & 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006936 (Box 17*)
  - You're Never Fully Dressed Without A Smile Vocal Selection, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 9; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006944 (Box 17*)
  - You Won't Be An Orphan For Long Vocal Selection, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 10; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006985 (Box 17*)
  - I Don't Need Anything But You, undated; From GOH's original production of Annie; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 12; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006993 (Box 17*)
  - Apples, Apples (Vocal Selections), undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 9; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007058 (Box 17*)
  - Tomorrow Vocal Selection, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy, also includes Bows, Cabinet Tomorrow, Entr'acte, and Walkoff; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007090 (Box 17*)
  - Maybe Vocal Selection, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy, also includes "Maybe" (reprise); Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 10; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007116 (Box 17*)
  - Annie's Letter, undated; From GOH's original production of Annie; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 3; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007132 (Box 17*)
  - We Got Annie Another Draft, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy, also includes copy w/o lyrics; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 34; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007140 (Box 17*)
  - Overture & "Entr' acte" from Annie, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 7; Dimensions: 9 x 12; Barcode: 35111000007157 (Box 17*)
  - That's The Way It Goes (Vocal Selections), undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 3; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11.75; Barcode: 35111000007165 (Box 17*)
  - I Think I'm Gonna Like It Here Vocal Selection, undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, photocopy, also includes "Cont'd" section; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 11; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007173 (Box 17*)
  - I've Never Been So Happy (Vocal Selections), undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 5; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007181 (Box 17*)
  - He Doesn't Know (Vocal Selections), undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 5; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000007199 (Box 17*)
  - I Don't Need Anything But You (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 26; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018063 (Box 18*)
  - Annie's Letter (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration (Cut on Broadway); Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 11; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018089 (Box 18*)
  - You Won't Be an Orphan For Long (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration Lost ?; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 25; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018097 (Box 18*)
  - Cabinet Tomorrow (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018048 (Box 18*)
  - Tomorrow (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 14; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018055 (Box 18*)
  - Something Was Missing (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 17; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018030 (Box 18*)
  - Hard Knock Life (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 15; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018022 (Box 18*)
  - Tomorrow Walkoff (Annie), undated; From GOH's orig. production of Annie, Original Orchestration; Items: 1; Format: Music Manuscript; Page count: 5; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000018105 (Box 18*)
  - Piano Book Masters, undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 111; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000018014 (Box 18*)
  - Russell Warner's Piano Book, undated; From GOH's original production of Annie, photocopy; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 78; Dimensions: 8.5 x 12.5; Barcode: 35111000018071 (Box 18*)
  - George Jessel, undated; Autographed photograph of George Jessel to Sam H. Harris; Items: 1; Format: Photograph; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 11 x 14; Barcode: 35111000006126 (Box 19*)
  - William Gillette, undated; Signed photo of William Gillette; Items: 1; Format: photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 9 x 13.5; Barcode: 35111000006134 (Box 19*)
  - The Cohan Revue 1918, undated; From Act II, "The Slave Market"; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 11 x 14; Barcode: 35111000006142 (Box 19*)
  - Adele Astaire, undated; Autographed, camera portrait by Hal Phyfe; Items: 1; Format: Photograph; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 14 x 11; Barcode: 35111000006159 (Box 19*)
  - The Red Widow, undated; Red Widow 1911; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 11 x 14; Barcode: 35111000006167 (Box 19*)
  - Chin-Chin, undated; Chin-Chin; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 11 x 14; Barcode: 35111000006175 (Box 19*)
  - Stepping Stones, undated; Autographed by Fred and Dorothy Stone, Globe Theatre 1923; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 9.5 x 13; Barcode: 35111000006225 (Box 19*)
  - Man Who Owns Broadway, undated; Nixon Theatre - Pittsburgh; Items: 1; Format: Booklet; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 4.5 x 6; Barcode: 35111000000780 (Box 20*)
  - The Life of Sarah Bernhardt, undated; 1880; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 36; Dimensions: 4.5 x 6; Barcode: 35111000000806 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress O'Keefe signed, Sarony Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002273 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Maggie Cline signed, Sarony Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002281 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Neilson in Twelfth Night; Items: 1; Format:; Page count: 1; Dimensions:; Barcode: 35111000002307 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Fanny Davenport as Princess Royal, Sarony Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002315 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Child actress "Little Tuesday" (The youngest comedienne in the world), Sarony Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002323 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Viola Allen; Items: 1; Format:; Page count: 1; Dimensions:; Barcode: 35111000002364 (Box 20*)
  - Edwin Booth, undated; Actor Edwin Booth- Head Shot wearing jacket and vest; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002406 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Composer Edward Solomon, signed to "A friend Keller"; Alex Bassano photographer London; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002588 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actor Louis Harrison, signed to Mrs Keller for Press Club Fair; Sarony Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002604 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actor Alfred Klein as Brother Pelican" in "Falka" 1884, by Falk; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002612 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Lavinia Shannon, signed on back "Indianapolis, Ind. Feb. 2nd, with love, Vinnie:" Kitchell Studio Indianapolis; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002638 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Lillian Russell, Sarony Studios, NY signed; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003123 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Lillian Russell; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002331 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Edna Wallace, signed, Sarony Studio, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003180 (Box 20*)